Contact

pamela.m88@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/murraypamela (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Theatre Social Media Management

Pamela Murray

Travelling in Argentina, previously at Intercom Argentina

Summary

Currently a language student in Argentina, recently Data Protection Officer for Intercom. Delivering and maintaining high impact, crossfunctional compliance programs. Experience working with global engineering, operations, sales, marketing and leadership teams to execute complex strategic and regulatory projects. Knowledgable in Data Protection Law (Adv Dip) and information systems auditing (CISA).

Experience

Intercom

Data Protection Officer/ Technical Program Manager May 2018 - November 2018 (7 months)

Intercom

2 years 4 months

Compliance Program Manager May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month) County Dublin, Ireland

Executive Assistant to Director of Engineering February 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Dublin

Creative Saint Helena
Director
January 2014 - December 2015 (2 years)
Jamestown, Saint Helena, South Atlantic

- Designed and implemented a program of cultural projects in Saint Helena.
- Built collaborative partnerships with island organisations including Human Rights Organisation, Public Library, Heritage Society, Women's Issues Saint Helena, The Arts and Crafts Association, Girl Guiding Association, Tourism,

Enterprise Saint Helena, Media Services, Social Services and Saint Helena Government.

Ouroboros Theatre Company
Company Manager/Producer
July 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 6 months)
Harcourt Terrace

-All duties relating to the roles of Producer and Company Secretary.

-Productions include Richard II (2013) at the Abbey Theatre and The Everyman Theatre Cork, Stoker (2012) at the Samuel Beckett Theatre and Making History (2012) at the American Conference for Irish Studies, New Orleans, USA.

Live Collision Festival
Associate Producer
February 2013 - April 2013 (3 months)

Project Arts Centre

Create Ireland
Research assistant
June 2011 - June 2012 (1 year 1 month)
Earl Street South. Dublin 8

Responsibilities:

- Researcher and assistant producer of The Collaborative Arts Performance Pack published by Create in July 2012.
- Engaged with and advised on the strategic aim and operation of The Collaborative Arts Performance Pack
- Analysed content and interactive elements of the resource.
- Researched artists and identified suitable practitioners to illustrate the specific elements of the resource,
- Liaised with selected practitioners and sought permissions, designers and scriptwriters

London Medical
Administrator/Project Co-ordinator
September 2009 - May 2011 (1 year 9 months)
Responsibilities:

- Project Management: Co-ordination of a medical advisory service to Axa Insurance and NHS diabetes Nottingham.
- Project Management: Co-ordination of the London Diabetes Protocol a comprehensive medical diabetes package.
- Marketing activities relating to London Diabetes Protocol, creating website profile and brochures.
- Private Secretary to Dr Simon Quantrill including miscellaneous administrative duties as required.
- Patient invoicing and account management using Sage, credit control,
 liaising with insurance companies on a daily basis.
- PA duties to CEO as required

Irish Family Planning Association Administrator/Receptionist September 2008 - August 2009 (1 year) Dublin

AMNCH Locum clerical officer 2006 - 2007 (2 years)

Education

The Honorable Society of King's Inns
Advanced Diploma in Data Protection Law (2017 - 2018)

Goldsmiths, University of London MA, Applied Theatre (2009 - 2011)

Dublin City University

BA, Economics, Politics and Law · (2006 - 2009)